Guide to the John Henry and Anna Botsford Comstock papers, 1833-1955,
Comstock, John Henry and Anna Botsford papers,
- Correspondence
  - John Henry Comstock professional correspondence
    - A-F
      - Foote, A.E., 1889-01-07 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Foote, A.E., 1890-07-10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Foote, A.E., 1890-07-17 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Foote, A.E., 1890-11-03 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Foote, A.E., 1891-03-26 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Foote, A.E., 1891-05-30 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Foote, A.E., 1893-10-20 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Foote, A.E., 1894-04-20 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Foote, A.E., Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1885-05-21 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        Illinois
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1886-03-06 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1887-05-07 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1887-05-23 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1888-01-27 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1888-02-23 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1889-03-23 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1889-05-23 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1889-06-06 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1889-06-20 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1890-05-13 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1891-07-27 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1891-10-01 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1892-03-25 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1892-04-25 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1892-08-18 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1893-08-22 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1893-11-03 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1894-03-15 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1894-04-02 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1894-09-20 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Forbes, Stephen Alfred, 1898-12-23 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Forbush, Edward Howe, 1894-07-16 (Box 6, Folder 10)
        Ornithologist
      - Foster, L.S., 1893-09-20 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Fowler, Charles Sumner, 1898-06-23 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Fowler, Charles Sumner, 1898-12-29 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Francis, Charles Spencer, 1898-08-17 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Francis, Mark, 1892-05-04 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        Texas
      - Franklin Educational Co., 1892-04-29 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Franklin Educational Co., 1892-07-18 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Frazar, M.A., 1892-07-25 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Frazar, M.A., 1892-08-02 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Frear, William, 1890-05-08 (Box 3, Folder 22)
        Newsdealer
      - Frear, William, 1894-09-19 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Freley, Jasper W., 1900-03-12 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - French, Abram and Co., 1888-02-17 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        Crockery, china, glass etc.
        Boston
      - French, C., 1892-10-18 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        Melbourne, Australia
      - French, C., 1892-11-19 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        missing)
      - French, George Hazen, 1891-03-07 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Freund, Charles, 1892-11-10 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        Geneva, New York
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1887-09-12 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1891-08-20 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1891-09-08 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1891-09-11 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1891-10-10 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1891-11-09 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1892-09-17 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Friedlander and Sohn, 1892-11-11 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Frost and Brown, 1890-12-26 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Frost, Ella, 1892-06-03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Frost, Ella, 1892-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Frost, Ella, 1892-08-30 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Frost, Ella, 1892-09-10 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Frost, George W., 1885-10-20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Grocer
      - Frost, George W., 1892-06-01 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Fuchs, Charles, 1892-02-04 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Fuertes, Estevan Antonio, 1889-09-14 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        Professor of Civil Engineering
      - Fuertes, Estevan Antonio, 1891-03-03 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Fuertes, Estevan Antonio, 1891-11-06 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Fuller, N.R., 1890-10-17 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - G-L
      - Gage, Simon Henry, 1886-01-31 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Gage, Simon Henry, 1892-11-12 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Gage, Simon Henry, 1894-03-14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Garman, Harison, 1891-06-06 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        Entomologist and Botanist
      - Garman, Harison, 1893-01-28 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Garman, Harison, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Garrettson and Co., 1890-12-13 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Gates, Alice (nee Jayne), 1896-08-24 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Gauntlett and Brooks, 1886-01-02 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Gauntlett and Brooks, 1886-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Gauntlett and Brooks, 1887-12-01 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Gauntlett and Brooks, 1890-01-01 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Gee, Reuben, 1893-04-18 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Gesner, Anthon Temple, 1888-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        clergyman
      - Geucke, Amy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Gibbs, Clarence A., 1888-07-10 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Gibbs, N., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Gifford, Albert, 1891-05-14 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Gilbert, E.P., 1890-04-11 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        Manager, Sage College, Cornell University
      - Gilbert, E.P., 1894-01-17 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Gilbert, E.P., 1894-02-20 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Gilbert, E.P., 1894-05-03 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1885-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
        Geologist, Charlemagne
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1886-01-10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1886-01-28 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1886-07-12 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1888-07-07 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1889-09-01 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1889-12-04 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1890-05-20 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1890-06-19 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1890-06-27 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1890-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1890-07-01 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-03-11 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-03-17 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-03-24 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-05-26 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-05-27 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-05-31 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1891-06-08 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-05-08 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-05-19 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-05-24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-06-01 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-06-10 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-06-22 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-06-24 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-08-20 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1892-09-12 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1893-05-22 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1893-06-10 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1893-09-25 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1896-11-26 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1897-10-04 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1899-03-28 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1900-08-19 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Gilbert, Grove Karl, 1900-08-22 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1885-05-15 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1885-10-02 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1890-02-15 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1891-02-10 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1893-12-24 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1894-06-10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Gillette, Clarence Preston, 1894-07-10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Ginn and Co., 1892-12-20 (Box 5, Folder 15)
        Publishers
      - Gleason and Co., 1886-01-12 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Gleed, Charles Sumner, 1892-06-24 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        Kansas
      - Gleed, Charles Sumner, 1892-09-14 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Gluck, James Fraser, 1885-06-09 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Gluck, James Fraser, 1885-06-10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Gluck, James Fraser, 1885-06-20 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Gluck, James Fraser, 1885-11-24 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Gluck, James Fraser, 1887-09-03 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Goddard, Martha, 1897-02-22 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Goding, Frederic Webster, 1884 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Maine
      - Goding, Frederic Webster, 1885-05-28 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Goding, Frederic Webster, 1885-07-10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Goding, Frederic Webster, 1886-04-17 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Goding, Frederic Webster, 1891-06-30 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Goding, Frederic Webster, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Goff, E.S., 1889-01-05 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Goff, E.S., 1889-09-19 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Goff, E.S., 1891-04-06 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Goodell, Henry Hill, 1894-04-13 (Box 6, Folder 8)
        President
      - Goss, B.F., 1891-02-08 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Grand Union Tea Co., 1892-09-28 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Grant, A.E., 1892-01-25 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Grant, Schuyler, 1890-07-10 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Grant, Schuyler, 1891-11-03 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Gray, Edward, 1891-12-31 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Gray, R.D., 1896-12-12 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Gray, William, 1890-06-26 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        Farmer
        Oswego, New York
      - Green, E. Ernest, 1893-04-22 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Green, E. Ernest, 1893-08-04 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Grindel, J.C., 1891-10-05 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Griswold, G.M., 1888-12-26 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Griswold, L.W., 1890-12-29 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Grote, A. Radcliff, 1897-04-05 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Grote, A. Radcliff, 1898-10-29 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Grote, A. Radcliff, 1899-03-04 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Grote, A. Radcliff, 1899-10-18 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Grote, A. Radcliff, 1899-12-12 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Grotecloss, Harriett Elizabeth (Hattie; Mrs. Charles David Marx), 1886-10-04 (Box 2, Folder 18)
        Zoololgy Teacher
        Framingham Massachusetts
      - Grotecloss, Harriett Elizabeth (Hattie; Mrs. Charles David Marx), 1886-10-17 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Grottenthaler, V., 1886-10-28 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Gully, F.A., 1885-07-06 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Gustav, Mayr, 1882-04-24 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Gustav, Mayr, 1883-06-18 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Gustav, Mayr, 1890-01-26 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Haag, F. and G., 1886-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Hagen, Hermann August, 1888-05-11 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Hair, U. and Son, 1890-03-21 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Hall, Edwin M., 1891-06-27 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        Carpet dealer
      - Hall, John, 1890-01-30 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Secretary
      - Hall, John, 1891-01-21 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Hallett, E.S., 1891-01-10 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Halsted, Byron David, 1885-10-21 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        Botanist
      - Halsted, Byron David, 1886-02-25 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Halsted, Byron David, 1886-06-17 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Hancock, Joseph L., 1889-07-10 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Hancock, Joseph L., 1889-07-18 (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Handsaker, J.T., 1892-01-21 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Hanford, Joel, 1889-10-19 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Hanford, Joel, 1890-04-18 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Hanford, Joel, 1890-04-22 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Hansen, Chris, 1889-05-22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Harding, William Elias, 1891-07-14 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Harlow, W.G., Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Harmony, Lewis, 1890-12-26 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Harper and Brothers, 1894-06-13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Harr, C.M., 1888-05-31 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Harrington, W.H., 1890-01-21 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Harrington, W.H., 1890-01-22 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Harrington, W.H., 1890-02-07 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Harrington, W.H., 1890-02-10 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Harris, George William, 1885-11-25 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Harris, George William, 1886-01-15 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Harris, George William, 1887-11-21 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Harris, George William, 1888-04-05 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Harris, George William, 1889-04-02 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Harris, George William, 1890 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Harris, George William, 1891-11-27 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Harris, George William, 1892-04-16 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Harris, George William, 1893-11-18 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Harris, George William, 1894-06-12 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Harris, H.F., 1891-02-13 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        secretary, The American Farmer Co., Cleveland
      - Harris, Samuel Gilbert, 1890-06-19 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        School Principal
        Ovid, New York
      - Harris, Samuel Gilbert, 1892-04-27 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Harris, Samuel Gilbert, 1892-05-03 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Harris, Samuel Gilbert, 1892-05-05 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Harris, Samuel Gilbert, 1892-06-03 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Harris, Samuel Gilbert, 1892-06-17 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Harshbarger, William Asbury, 1891-11-11 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Hart, Charles A., 1890-12-11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Hart, Charles A., 1891-08-26 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Hart, Charles A., 1892-01-04 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Harvey, F.L., 1886-01-17 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Professor of Natural History
      - Harvey, F.L., 1888-11-05 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Harvey, F.L., 1889-01-24 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Harvey, F.L., 1889-05-23 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Harvey, F.L., 1891-01-29 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Harvey, F.L., 1891-02-09 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Harvey, L., 1882-05-12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Hasbrouck, Maude Estelle, 1891-12-10 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Havens, Charles Harrison, 1889-01-12 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Hawkins Todd Co., 1888-07-17 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Hawkins Todd Co., 1888-11-09 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Hawkins Todd Co., 1889-12-10 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Hayes, H.A., 1887-09-26 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Hayes, H.A., 1888-04-13 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Hayes, H.A., 1888-04-15 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Hayes, H.A., 1888-11-21 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Hayes, H.A., 1889-12-07 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Haynes, B.L., 1893-01-10 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Haywood, Albert, 1888-06-13 (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Heall, J.W., 1886-09-18 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Heard, Thomas H., 1890-12-15 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-02-25 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-03-15 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-03-17 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-04-08 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-04-14 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-04-20 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Heddon, James, 1886-04-22 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Heddon, James, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Heffron and Driscoll, 1887-05-17 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Heffron and Driscoll, 1887-09-30 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Heffron and Driscoll, 1887-10-31 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Heffron and Driscoll, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Heller, Michael Burt, 1889-12-20 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Henderson, Louis Fourniquet, 1890-08-15 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Henderson, Louis Fourniquet, 1894-11-03 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Henderson, Louis Fourniquet, 1899-05-30 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Henderson, Peter and Co., 1889-11-07 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        Seedsman
      - Hendricks and Co., 1890-09-03 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Henning, Carl F., 1889-12-12 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Henning, Carl F., 1890-11-24 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1882-04-15 (Box 2, Folder 2)
        Professor of Agriculture
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1882-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1883-01-23 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1888-05-02 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1888-05-10 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1890-09-29 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Henry, William Arnon, 1890-10-21 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1886-01-10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1886-01-19 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1886-01-28 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1888-03-03 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1889-10-24 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1889-12-14 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1890-03-24 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1890-04-02 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1891-01-01 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1893-11-08 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1894-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1894-07-15 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1894-08-31 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1897-07-01 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Henshaw, Samuel, 1900-01-01 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Herpers, H., 1891-06-01 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Herrick and Co., 1892-11-10 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Herrick, Glenn Washington, 1898-11-08 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Hess, Selmar, 1885-10-20 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Hess, Selmar, 1886-01-29 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Hewett, Waterman Thomas, 1896-03-26 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Hibbard, Horace Mack, 1894-05-21 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Hibbard, S. Bn., 1887-02-21 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        Treasurer, President White Memorial Fund
      - Hickey, Isaac, 1890-05-22 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Hicks, G.H., 1894-09-01 (Box 6, Folder 11)
        Department of Agriculture, Botany Division
        Washington, D.C.
      - Higley, Warren, 1891-05-26 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1888-10-24 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1888-10-30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1888-11-08 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1888-12-10 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1888-12-11 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1889-10-26 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Hildreth Brothers, 1890-02-03 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Hilgard, Eugene Woldemar, 1892-01-27 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        Director, Agricultural Experiment Station, University of California
      - Hill and Watkins, 1892-01-18 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Hill and Yard, 1892-04-26 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Hill, C.J., 1891-08-08 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Hill, E.D., 1891-11-21 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Hill, E.D., 1892-11-26 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Hill, Franklin C., 1888-10-08 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Hill, Mary Ellen, 1893-06-24 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Hill, Robert Thomas, 1886-03-24 (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Geologist
      - Hill, Robert Thomas, 1887-02-10 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Hill, Robert Thomas, 1888-07-31 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Hill, Robert Thomas, 1892-07-09 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Hill, Robert Thomas, 1892-07-28 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1891-01-17 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1891-02-21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1891-07-18 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1892-06-20 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1892-07-09 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1893-07-21 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1893-07-24 (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Hillabrant, J.W., 1894-07-24 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Hillick, Charles H., 1890-02-14 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Hillman, Fred H., 1890-09-10 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        Agricultural Experiment Station
        Nevada
      - Hillman, Fred H., 1890-10-28 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Hillman, Fred H., 1891-01-19 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Hillman, Fred H., 1892-12-03 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Hitchcock, Romyn, 1887-05-09 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        Chemist
      - Hitchcock, Romyn, 1890-08-13 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Hittell, Katie, 1892-03-11 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Hittell, Katie, 1892-03-15 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Hoag, C.L., 1885-05-19 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Hoag, Ernest Bryant, 1894-01-04 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Hodder, Frank Heywood, 1890-01-30 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Professor of History
      - Hodges, Nathaniel Dana Carlile, 1886-07-19 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        Editor, Science Weekly
      - Hodges, Nathaniel Dana Carlile, 1888-08-21 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Hodges, Nathaniel Dana Carlile, 1890-05-09 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Hoffman, D.A., 1886-03-09 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1886-04-15 (Box 2, Folder 12)
        E.M. and H.N. Hoffman, nursery
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1886-07-01 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1886-08-17 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1888-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1889-04-21 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1889-06-03 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1890-01-14 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Hoffman, Harry Natt, 1890-09-02 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Hoffman, J.W., 1890-03-10 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Hoffman, J.W., 1890-06-07 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Hoick, Charles Franklin, 1893-06-11 (Box 5, Folder 18)
        Terre Haute, Indiana
      - Hoick, Charles Franklin, 1894-05-02 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Holden, John, 1890-07-20 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Hollrung, D.M., 1892-01-29 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Hollrung, D.M., 1893-08-05 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Holmes, Ella Amanda, 1899-11-05 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Holmes, Joseph Austin, 1888-09-05 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Holmes, Manfred James, 1899-04-10 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Holt, Henry and Co., 1890-08-25 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Holt, Henry and Co., 1893-08-07 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Holzinger, John Michael, 1889-01-14 (Box 3, Folder 6)
        Museum curator, St. Normal School
      - Hooper, Franklin William, 1898-08-16 (Box 6, Folder 17)
        Director, Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences
      - Hooper, Franklin William, 1899-03-10 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Hopkins, Andrew Delmar, 1894-04-12 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Hopkins, Andrew Delmar, 1894-10-25 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Hopkins, Grant Sherman, 1892-08-31 (Box 5, Folder 11)
        anatomy
      - Hopkins, L.D.C. and Son, 1893-10-20 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Horr, Mabel Howes Hebard, 1891-08-08 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        Mrs. Ch. Wm. Horr
      - Horr, Norton Townshend, 1890-08-14 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Horton, Elmer Grant, 1892-05-13 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Hosford, J. Spencer, 1890-05-20 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1891-10-12 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1891-10-19 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1892-11-17 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - House, George E., 1894-07-10 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Hovey, George H., 1888-11-01 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Hovey, George H., 1891-08-31 (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1886-05-14 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1887-01-18 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1887-01-28 (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1887-10-03 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1887-10-10 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1887-10-11 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Howard, Leland Ossian (Leal), 1888-03-10 (Box 2, Folder 28)